https://www.trichemicals.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Home
Privacy Policy
At TRInternational, your privacy is very important to us. We appreciate you visiting our website and understand the value of protecting your privacy.
When you visit our site we use Common Logfile Format Tracking Software to collect the following non-personal information about your visit. Your Internet Protocol Address and domain name used but not the email address. (Your Internet Protocol address is a numerical identifier assigned either to your Internet service provider or directly to your computer.) The type of browser and operating system you used, the date and time you visited this site, the web pages or services you accessed at this site and the website you visited prior to coming to this one. These items simply help us understand what is important to our visitors and in no way personally identifies you to anyone.
We will collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, postal address, telephone and mobile numbers, e-mail address, when you provide it to us while on this Site such as when you fill out the Request for Quote on our Contact Us. Also if you use any of the email links provided on our website you are most often requesting a response from us. The information you provide in these emails is used to respond directly to your questions or comments you may have. We will not disclose, sell or trade any information sent from you to us to any outside sources for any reason.
TRInternational has many useful links to other websites. When you link to another site, you are no longer on TRInternational and this privacy policy will not apply. When you link to another web site, you are subject to the privacy policy of that new site.
Thank you from all of us at TRInternational and we hope you enjoy your visit and find our website useful.
